<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interview on R-Ladies Lausanne</title>
    <link>/tags/interview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interview on R-Ladies Lausanne</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/interview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>News August 2018</title>
      <link>/post/2018/08/03/news-august-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/08/03/news-august-2018/</guid>
      <description>Since our last newsletter in May a few things have happened:
 In June we had our 4th meetup before the summer break, R-Ladies Global launched a new Community Slack, and we caught up with two of our speakers in an interview.  We are currently planning our meetups in Autumn, with the first meetup being in October ➡️ check our meetup page for updates.
We are also looking for speakers and venues, please contact us via lausanne@rladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Elizaveta Semenova</title>
      <link>/post/2018/07/31/interview-elizaveta-semenova/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/07/31/interview-elizaveta-semenova/</guid>
      <description>I think there is a lot of power in the Bayesian approach. The problem is the high entrance threshold due to the computational issues that it poses. So I am always very happy to talk about the benefits of Bayesian statistics and show how simple a model can look like.
 In past April, Elizaveta Semenova  gave an introduction to Bayesian inference in R, using Stan at our third meetup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interview with Elisabeth Dahlqwist</title>
      <link>/post/2018/05/10/presenter-2-elisabeth-dahlqwist/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2018/05/10/presenter-2-elisabeth-dahlqwist/</guid>
      <description>The reason I presented at R-Ladies, is, that when I had done my first shiny app, I felt it was really amazing and I really wanted to share my experience of doing that, because it was quite easy.
 Elisabeth Dahlqwist  gave an introduction to Shiny at our second R-Ladies Lausanne meetup.


Sina R&amp;uuml;eger: What is the work that you do? Elisabeth Dahlqwist: I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in Biostatistics at Karoliska Institute in Stockholm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>